We were lost inside A hollow sound Stuck on
repeat Running circles in the ground You were
the starter I was the engine A story told by
someone else's invention
The panic's gone, the signal's clear We found a
switch and faced the fear This is outrage, this
is release We finally found our own true peace
We're starting over, wiping the slate clean
This is a brand new start on a stage you've seen
We're coming home, we're breaking through This
is the sound we always knew It's not a hard reset
It's just the first time it's been through
They tried to break us Tried to tear us down They
stole the signal They stole the crown But we're
the ones Who own the stage It's time to turn a
brand new page We're starting over, wiping the
slate clean. This is a brand new start, stengen
scene. We're coming home, we're breaking
through. This is the sound we always knew It's
not a hard reset It's just the first time it's
been true
Yes!
We are the cosmos, we are the fire We're taking
this one higher and higher
We're starting over, wiping the slate clean.
This is a brand new start-up stench and scene.
We're coming home, we're breaking through.
This is the sound we always knew It's not a hard
reset It's just the first time it's been true
A brand new scene
We're coming home